BINTANG RIZQI KHAIRULLAH

Bekasi, 17530 | (62) 852-1180-3990 | Bintangrizqi21@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/bintang-rizqi-khairullah | github.com/bintangrizqi public.tableau.com/app/profile/bintang.rizqi.khairullah

SUMMARY

Bachelor of Statistics, offer strong work ethics, responsible, and proactive. I always looks for innovation that could improve my work's quality. Experienced in creating automated excel template to create fast, accurate, and easy to read reports.

EXPERIENCE

Sales Administrator

Bekasi, August 2022 - Present

Coca – Cola Europacific Partners

- Supported the sales team by creating daily reports using automated Microsoft excel.
- Coordinated with the Sales and Key Account teams to perform data maintenance.

Statistician Intern

Jakarta, June 2020 - August 2020

Ministry of Agriculture, Secretariat Directorate General of Horticulture

- Used R programming language to perform data analysis using panel data.
- Identified factors that would increase shallot's production.

Staff of Data Analyst Department

Bogor, November 2019 – November 2020

Student Profession Association Gamma Sigma Beta

- Diagnosed the cause of statistics assumption violation of client's statistical analysis.
- Provided suggestion to clients how to deal with the violation of statistics assumption.

EDUCATION

IPB University

Bogor, September 2017 – April 2022

Bachelor of Statistics, Honors: Cum Laude (GPA: 3.56/4.00)

Thesis:" Geographical and Temporally Weighted Regression to Modelling Poverty Rates in Central Java in 2017-2019"

SMAN 1 Tambun Selatan

Bekasi, July 2014 – May 2017

Mathematic and Natural Science, National Exam Score: 88.00/100.00

SKILLS

MS Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint) | Python (Pandas, Matplotlib, NumPy, Scikit-learn) | R (ggplot, GWmodel, Imtest)

PROJECTS

House Price Prediction

Bekasi, September 2023 – Present

Student Profession Association Gamma Sigma Beta

- Data exploration using Microsoft excel to gain hypothesis.
- Performing data modelling using RStudio.